companywiki.in 2015-12-21

# Privacy-Policy | Companywiki

This privacy policy sets out how [ companywiki.in ](http://www.companywiki.in/ "companywiki") uses and protects any information that you give it when you use this website. [ companywiki.in ](http://www.companywiki.in/ "companywiki") is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

[companywiki.in ](http://www.companywiki.in/ "companywiki") may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st January 2013

### What we collect

  * We may collect the following information:
  * name , job title, organization
  * contact information including email address and mobile number

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
  * We will not share your information with any Third Party for any marketing related activity.
  * We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
  * We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at the details given in our [ Contact Us ](http://www.companywiki.in/contact-us "Contact Us") page.
